zolahost.com 2019-05-31

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which ZolaHost collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the zolahost.com Website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by ZolaHost.com.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use ”cookies” to enhance User experience. User web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and some time to track information about them. User may want to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to notify you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

We may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

– To improve customer service  
– To personalize user experience  
– To process order

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. Our Site is also in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

ZolaHost has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users frequently tocheck this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

<http://zolahost.com/contact>

Z Hosting Technologies  
264, Kovai Road, Kundadam  
Dharapuram,Tirupur,  
Tamil Nadu-638702,  
india.  
[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

This document was last updated on Jun 02, 2011
